http://www.isbn.org/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
R.R. Bowker, LLC ("Bowker") owns and operates this website.
Our postal address is:
R.R. Bowker
630 Central Ave.
New Providence, NJ 07974
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please contact us by sending an e-mail to techsupport@bowker.com or by writing to the above postal address, Attention: Marketing Department.
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy Bowker provides this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home pages and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
This notice applies to all information collected from or submitted to all Bowker websites.
Outside Links
Bowker has several links to outside resources in an effort to help individuals gather information. Bowker is not responsible for the content provided on these sites, their privacy policies, or how they treat information about their users.
Some links, primarily to book industry sites and entities, are provided as a service to our users. Other links to suppliers are available as part of paid advertising packages.
Data Gathering & Usage
Bowker collects the domain names and e-mail addresses (where possible) of visitors and subscribers to our websites and the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. We aggregate information on what pages visitors and subscribers access or visit, as well as information volunteered by the visitor (such as survey information and/or site registrations).
The information we collect is used for internal review to improve the content of our websites, used to compile internal statistical and usage information, used to notify visitors and subscribers about updates to our websites, used to inform visitors and subscribers of other Bowker products or services they may be interested in, and used to inform visitors and subscribers of helpful products or services offered by others. Visitors and subscribers who provide their mailing address, telephone number, and/or e-mail address may be contacted for these purposes using any of these methods.
Electronic "cookies" are codes placed on your hard drive to enable sites to recognize if you have been there before. Cookies are given to visitors and subscribers of our websites so that Bowker can keep track of the domain from which people visit.
We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies or third party advertising agencies that track certain Internet activity.
From time to time, we may use information collected and supplied by visitors and subscribers for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our websites to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.
If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should refer to this online privacy policy page periodically.
Opt Out
Visitors and subscribers who have supplied us with information may adjust their privacy preferences for receiving e-mail, postal or telephone communications from Bowker and/or other organizations this information is shared with by e-mailing us at the above address or writing to us at the above postal address.
Access or Correct Your Information
Upon request we can provide visitors and subscribers with access to a description of information that we maintain about them. We also offer visitors and subscribers the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Visitors and subscribers may request this information, or have this information corrected, by e-mailing us at the above address or writing to us at the above postal address.
Data Security
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
Google Analytics and Remarketing
We use a service provided by Google called Google Analytics (GA). GA permits us to reach people who have previously visited our site, and show them relevant advertisements when they visit other sites across the Internet in the Google Display Network. This is often called ‘remarketing’.
Cookies can be used to track your session on our website, to serve customized ads from Google and other third party vendors. When you visit this website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other third parties. Through first-party and third party cookies, these third parties may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this website and across the Internet based on your prior visits to this website and elsewhere on the Internet. We do not collect this information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see.
Opting Out
Of Google Analytics
You may be able to opt out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager (http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/), and the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on (http://www.google.ca/ads/preferences/plugin/).
Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with remarketing ads using GA and cookies from other third party vendors based on your prior visits to this website and elsewhere on the Internet.
Contact Us
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please contact us by sending an e-mail to techsupport@bowker.com
or writing to the above postal address, Attention: Marketing Department.
Bowker is an affiliated business of ProQuest. | © 2014 R.R. Bowker LLC. All rights reserved. For support, please call us toll-free at 1-877-310-7333.Contact Us | ISBN Terms of Use| Bowker Statement of Use
| Privacy Policy
